$CampfireGameplayPage	Gameplay
$CampfireAdvancedPage	Advanced
$CampfireHelpPage	Help
$CampfireSaveLoadPage	Save/Load
$CampfireGameplayHeaderCamping	Camping
$CampfireGameplayHeaderHotkeys	Hotkeys
$CampfireGameplayHeaderTentDisplay	Player Tent Behavior
$CampfireGameplayHeaderFollowerTentDisplay	Follower Tent Behavior
$CampfireAdvancedHeaderPlacement	Object Placement
$CampfireAdvancedHeaderSystem	Campfire System
$CampfireHelpHeaderTutorials	Tutorials
$CampfireSaveLoadHeaderProfile	Settings Profiles
$CampfireHelpHeaderTroubleshooting	Troubleshooting Wizards
$CampfireGuideHeader	Player's Guide
$CampfireGameplaySettingCampingRemoveGear	Player Removes Gear in Tents
$CampfireGameplaySettingCampingLightingMode	Manually Light Campfires
$CampfireGameplaySettingLegality	Camping Illegal in Settled Areas
$CampfireGameplaySettingFlammability	Camping Equipment Can Burn
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowHelm	Remove Helm / Head Gear (See Note)
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowCuirass	Remove Armor / Clothing
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowGauntlets	Remove Gauntlets / Gloves
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowBoots	Remove Boots / Shoes (See Note)
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowBackpack	Remove Backpack
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowWeapons	Remove Weapons
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowShield	Remove Shield
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowAmmo	Remove Ammo
$CampfireGameplaySettingFollowersInteract	Followers Interact with Campsite
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowFollowerGear	Followers Remove Gear in Tents
$CampfireGameplayHotkeyCreateItem	Survival Skill: Create Item
$CampfireGameplayHotkeyBuildCampfire	Survival Skill: Build Campfire
$CampfireGameplayHotkeyHarvestWood	Survival Skill: Harvest Wood
$CampfireGameplayHotkeyInstincts	Survival Skill: Instincts
$CampfireAdvancedSettingAdvancedPlacement	Advanced Object Placement
$CampfireAdvancedSettingMaxThreads	Max Placement Threads
$CampfireGameplaySettingTrackFollowers	Track Followers
$CampfireSaveLoadCurrentProfile	Current Profile:
$CampfireSaveLoadRenameProfile	Rename Profile
$CampfireSaveLoadAboutProfiles	About Settings Profiles
$CampfireSaveLoadSettingsSaved	All settings saved successfully.
$CampfireSaveLoadEnable	Automatic Profile Save / Load
$CampfireGuideTopic1	Building Campfires
$CampfireGuideTopic2	Supplies
$CampfireGuideTopic3	Harvesting Wood
$CampfireGuideTopic4	Backpacks
$CampfireGuideTopic5	Campfire Perk System
$CampfireGuideTopic6	Instincts
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingCampingArmorTentsText	If enabled, you will remove certain pieces of gear when sitting or lying down inside a tent, and display those items inside. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingCampingFireLightingText	If enabled, You must light campfires yourself by hitting them with a torch or using a flame spell or shout.\nIf disabled, campfires are lit as soon as you build them.\nDefault: Off
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingLegality	If enabled, you will be unable to place camping equipment near cities or inside houses, inns, and other owned spaces. You can still place camping equipment in the wilderness and inside dungeons and caves.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingFlammability	If enabled, certain pieces of camping equipment will be flammable, and can begin to burn when hit with a torch, flame spell, or shout. The fire can be put out with a frost spell before the item becomes consumed. If fire engulfs the item, it will be destroyed.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowHelm	If enabled, you will remove your helm or head gear and place it inside your tent when you sit or lie down. It is re-equipped when you get back up.\nNote: Self-enchanted head gear will not re-apply enchantment effects after getting out of a tent. This is a game engine issue. Disable if you use self-enchanted head gear.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowCuirass	If enabled, you will remove your armor or clothing and place it inside your tent when you sit or lie down. It is re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowBoots	If enabled, you will remove your boots or shoes and place them inside your tent when you sit or lie down. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nNote: Self-enchanted foot gear will not re-apply enchantment effects after getting out of a tent. This is a game engine issue. Disable if you use self-enchanted foot gear.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowGauntlets	If enabled, you will remove your gloves or gauntlets and place them inside your tent when you sit or lie down. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowBackpack	If enabled, you will remove your backpack and place it inside your tent when you sit or lie down. It is re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowWeapons	If enabled, you will remove your weapons and place them inside your tent when you sit or lie down. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowShield	If enabled, you will remove your shield and place it near your tent when you sit or lie down. It is re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowAmmo	If enabled, you will remove your quiver or crossbow bolts when you sit or lie down. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nNote: Ammo is not displayed in tents.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightFollowersInteract	If enabled, your followers (up to 3) will sleep in spare bed rolls when you lay down, and sit inside a tent or near campfires when you do.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowFollowerGear	If enabled, your followers will remove their worn weapons and shield, and place them inside your tent when sitting or sleeping.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightHKCreateItem	Click to set a key to quickly use the Survival Skill: Create Item ability.\nThis will remove the Survival Skill: Create Item power from your spell list. Default the hotkey to acquire the power again.
$CampfireOptionHighlightHKBuildCampfire	Click to set a key to quickly use the Survival Skill: Build Campfire ability.\nThis will remove the Survival Skill: Build Campfire power from your spell list. Default the hotkey to acquire the power again.
$CampfireOptionHighlightHKHarvestWood	Click to set a key to quickly use the Survival Skill: Harvest Wood ability.\nThis will remove the Survival Skill: Harvest Wood power from your spell list. Default the hotkey to acquire the power again.
$CampfireOptionHighlightHKInstincts	Click to set a key to quickly use the Survival Skill: Instincts ability.\nThis will remove the Survival Skill: Instincts power from your spell list. Default the hotkey to acquire the power again.
$CampfireOptionHighlightAdvancedPlacement	If enabled, the placement indicator will follow where you look and move, and snap to the slope of the terrain. This allows for very precise placement. If you are experiencing performance issues, try disabling this feature to place items in a simpler way (indicator doesn't follow movements or snap to terrain).\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingMaxThreads	When placing camping equipment, the system distributes the calculations across many threads in order to place the object faster. This especially speeds up placing multi-part objects, like tents. The system can use up to 30 threads.\nIf you are experiencing undesired behavior when placing tents or other objects, try reducing the maximum number of threads.\nDefault: 20
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingTrackFollowers	If enabled, Campfire will track 3 of your nearest followers and your pet, if any. This enables features like followers sleeping in the bed rolls of tents. This information is also shared with other Campfire-dependent mods.\nIf disabled, Campfire will not track followers, and ALL follower features in Campfire AND ANY OTHER CAMPFIRE-BASED MOD will be DISABLED. Disabling this feature is not recommended.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingTutorials	If enabled, Campfire will display certain tutorial messages when it is contextually relevant. If you are already an experienced Campfire player, you can safely disable this feature.\nDefault: On
$CampfireTutorialResetPrompt	Reset all tutorials?
$CampfireHelpTroubleshootingSelectProblem	Select Problem:
$CampfireTroubleshooterPrompt	This will run the troubleshooter. You will have to exit the menus in order to complete the troubleshooting procedure. Continue?
$CampfireTroubleshooting0	Select
$CampfireTroubleshooting1	Always says "You are already trying to place something."
$CampfireHelpSettingTutorialsShow	Show Contextual Tutorials
$CampfireHelpSettingTutorialsReset	Reset Tutorials
$CampfireGuideTopic1Text	To build a campfire, use the Build Campfire ability (by selecting it in the Spell menu and pressing Shout). Campfires can be created from a variety of items, displayed in the crafting menu.\n\nTinder is required to start a campfire. Different kinds of tinder have different chances of successfully lighting your campfire. It is much harder to light a campfire in bad weather, so prepare by carrying some high-quality tinder in case the weather takes a turn for the worse.
$CampfireGuideTopic2Text	Creating or buying supplies can aid you in a wide variety of circumstances. You can create supplies such as tanning racks, torches, basic weapons, and more by using the Survival Skill: Create Item ability.\n\nSome supplies can be purchased at various general goods merchants.
$CampfireGuideTopic3Text	To harvest wood, use Survival Skill: Harvest Wood. If you have a woodcutter's axe or a stone hatchet, you will be able to harvest deadwood.\n\nWithout an axe, you can harvest branches.\n\nEach time you search for resources, an hour will pass.
$CampfireGuideTopic4Text	The amount of additional equipment required to survive in the wilderness can be burdensome. Backpacks can help offset the weight of the additional gear.\n\nBackpacks are created at a tanning rack from a wide variety of pelts. They can be combined with amulets of the Nine Divines to impart certain bonuses and provide additional customization.
$CampfireGuideTopic5Text	Campfire includes a stand-alone perk system to improve your ability to start fires, harvest more resources, improve your Instincts, and more.\n\nTo access the perk system, build a campfire and select Skills. Other Campfire-based mods can add their own perk trees to this menu, like Frostfall and Last Seed.
$CampfireGuideTopic6Text	Instincts allows you to focus on your senses of hearing and smell when outdoors.\n\nWhen Instincts is active, you will see sound emit from creatures (including machines and daedra) up to 100 feet away. You can only "hear" creatures this way when they are moving, talking, or loud (like using a forge). If they are close (at least 50 feet), they can be "heard" even when quiet and still, but the effect is faint.
$CampfireGuideTopic6TextCont	Dead bodies can be "smelled", including the undead. Items in the environment that can be used as tinder for campfires will glow.\n\nThis ability can only be used outdoors, and movement cancels the effect.