$CampfireGameplayPage	Gameplay
$CampfireInstinctsPage	Instincts
$CampfireAdvancedPage	Advanced
$CampfireHelpPage	Help
$CampfireSaveLoadPage	Profiles
$CampfireGameplayHeaderCamping	Camping
$CampfireGameplayHeaderHotkeys	Hotkeys
$CampfireGameplayHeaderTentDisplay	Player Tent Behavior
$CampfireGameplayHeaderFollowerTentDisplay	Follower Behavior
$CampfireAdvancedHeaderPlacement	Object Placement
$CampfireAdvancedHeaderSystem	Campfire System
$CampfireAdvancedHeaderCompatibility	Compatibility
$CampfireAdvancedHeaderCampingSkill	Camping Skill
$CampfireHelpHeaderTutorials	Tutorials
$CampfireSaveLoadHeaderProfile	Settings Profiles
$CampfireHelpHeaderTroubleshooting	Troubleshooting Wizards
$CampfireGuideHeader	Player's Guide
$CampfireCampfireModeQuick	Quick
$CampfireCampfireModeRealistic	Realistic
$CampfireGameplaySettingCampfireMode	Campfire Building
$CampfireGameplaySettingCampingRemoveGear	Player Removes Gear in Tents
$CampfireGameplaySettingCampingLightingMode	Manually Light Campfires
$CampfireGameplaySettingLegality	Camping Illegal in Settled Areas
$CampfireGameplaySettingFlammability	Camping Equipment Can Burn
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowHelm	Remove Helm / Head Gear (See Note)
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowCuirass	Remove Armor / Clothing
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowGauntlets	Remove Gauntlets / Gloves
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowBoots	Remove Boots / Shoes (See Note)
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowBackpack	Remove Backpack
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowWeapons	Remove Weapons
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowShield	Remove Shield
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowAmmo	Remove Ammo
$CampfireGameplaySettingFollowersInteract	Followers Interact with Campsite
$CampfireGameplaySettingShowFollowerGear	Followers Remove Gear in Tents
$CampfireGameplayHotkeyCreateItem	Survival Skill: Create Item
$CampfireGameplayHotkeyBuildCampfire	Survival Skill: Build Campfire
$CampfireGameplayHotkeyHarvestWood	Survival Skill: Harvest Wood
$CampfireGameplayHotkeyInstincts	Survival Skill: Instincts
$CampfireAdvancedSettingAdvancedPlacement	Advanced Object Placement
$CampfireAdvancedSettingMaxThreads	Max Placement Threads
$CampfireGameplaySettingTrackFollowers	Track Followers
$CampfireAdvancedSettingEOCompatibility	Equipping Overhaul
$CampfireAdvancedSettingEOCompatibilityNotInstalled	Equipping Overhaul (Not Installed)
$CampfireAdvancedCampingSkillRespec	Respec Skill Points
$CampfireAdvancedCampingSkillRespecConfirm	Are you sure you want to refund all earned Camping skill points so you can reallocate them?
$CampfireAdvancedCampingSkillRestore	Restore Skill Progress
$CampfireAdvancedCampingSkillRestoreConfirm	This option is intended to be used to reclaim Camping skill progress that was lost due to a clean save or mod uninstallation. Do you wish to continue?
$CampfireAdvancedCampingSkillRestoreAmount	Points to Restore
$CampfireAdvancedCampingSkillRestoreSelect	Select the total number of skill points to restore. This will replace your current progress.
$CampfireAdvancedCampingSkillRestoreDone	Skill points restored successfully.
$CampfireSaveLoadCurrentProfile	Current Profile:
$CampfireSaveLoadRenameProfile	Rename Profile
$CampfireSaveLoadAboutProfiles	About Settings Profiles
$CampfireSaveLoadSettingsSaved	All settings saved successfully.
$CampfireSaveLoadConfirm	Load the selected profile?
$CampfireSaveLoadEnable	Automatic Profile Save / Load
$CampfireSaveLoadDefaultProfile	Default Current Profile
$CampfireSaveLoadRenameErrorBlank	The profile name cannot be blank.
$CampfireSaveLoadDefaultProfileConfirm	Are you sure you want to restore all settings on your current profile to their default values?
$CampfireSkyUI51Required	SkyUI 5.1+ Required
$CampfireGuideTopic1	Building Campfires
$CampfireGuideTopic2	Supplies
$CampfireGuideTopic3	Harvesting Wood
$CampfireGuideTopic4	Backpacks
$CampfireGuideTopic5	Skill System
$CampfireGuideTopic6	Instincts
$CampfireOptionHighlightCampfireMode	Quick: 4 firewood or deadwood is used, and the campfire is lit automatically.\nRealistic: You must use tinder, starting fuel, and lighting the campfire takes skill and time.\nDefault: Realistic
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingCampingArmorTentsText	If enabled, you will remove certain pieces of gear when sitting or lying down inside a tent, and display those items inside. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingCampingFireLightingText	If enabled, You must light campfires yourself by hitting them with a torch or using a flame spell or shout.\nIf disabled, campfires are lit as soon as you build them.\nDefault: Off
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingLegality	If enabled, you will be unable to place camping equipment near cities or inside houses, inns, and other owned spaces. You can still place camping equipment in the wilderness and inside dungeons and caves.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingFlammability	If enabled, certain pieces of camping equipment will be flammable, and can begin to burn when hit with a torch, flame spell, or shout. The fire can be put out with a frost spell before the item becomes consumed. If fire engulfs the item, it will be destroyed.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowHelm	If enabled, you will remove your helm or head gear and place it inside your tent when you sit or lie down. It is re-equipped when you get back up.\nNote: Self-enchanted head gear will not re-apply enchantment effects after getting out of a tent. This is a game engine issue. Disable if you use self-enchanted head gear.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowCuirass	If enabled, you will remove your armor or clothing and place it inside your tent when you sit or lie down. It is re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowBoots	If enabled, you will remove your boots or shoes and place them inside your tent when you sit or lie down. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nNote: Self-enchanted foot gear will not re-apply enchantment effects after getting out of a tent. This is a game engine issue. Disable if you use self-enchanted foot gear.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowGauntlets	If enabled, you will remove your gloves or gauntlets and place them inside your tent when you sit or lie down. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowBackpack	If enabled, you will remove your backpack and place it inside your tent when you sit or lie down. It is re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowWeapons	If enabled, you will remove your weapons and place them inside your tent when you sit or lie down. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowShield	If enabled, you will remove your shield and place it near your tent when you sit or lie down. It is re-equipped when you get back up.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowAmmo	If enabled, you will remove your quiver or crossbow bolts when you sit or lie down. They are re-equipped when you get back up.\nNote: Ammo is not displayed in tents.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightFollowersInteract	If enabled, your followers (up to 3) will sleep in spare bed rolls when you lay down, and sit inside a tent or near campfires when you do.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightShowFollowerGear	If enabled, your followers will remove their worn weapons and shield, and place them inside your tent when sitting or sleeping.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightHKCreateItem	Click to set a key to quickly use the Survival Skill: Create Item ability.\nThis will remove the Survival Skill: Create Item power from your spell list. Default the hotkey to acquire the power again.
$CampfireOptionHighlightHKBuildCampfire	Click to set a key to quickly use the Survival Skill: Build Campfire ability.\nThis will remove the Survival Skill: Build Campfire power from your spell list. Default the hotkey to acquire the power again.
$CampfireOptionHighlightHKHarvestWood	Click to set a key to quickly use the Survival Skill: Harvest Wood ability.\nThis will remove the Survival Skill: Harvest Wood power from your spell list. Default the hotkey to acquire the power again.
$CampfireOptionHighlightHKInstincts	Click to set a key to quickly use the Survival Skill: Instincts ability.\nThis will remove the Survival Skill: Instincts power from your spell list. Default the hotkey to acquire the power again.
$CampfireOptionHighlightAdvancedPlacement	If enabled, the placement indicator will follow where you look and move, and snap to the slope of the terrain. This allows for very precise placement. If you are experiencing performance issues, try disabling this feature to place items in a simpler way (indicator doesn't follow movements or snap to terrain).\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingMaxThreads	When placing camping equipment, the system distributes the work across "threads" to place the object faster. This helps speed up placing complex objects, like tents. The system can use up to 30 threads. If you are experiencing undesired behavior when placing tents or other objects, try reducing the maximum number of threads.\nDefault: 20
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingTrackFollowers	If enabled, Campfire will track 3 of your nearest followers and your pet. This enables features like followers sleeping in the bed rolls of tents. If disabled, ALL follower features in Campfire AND ANY OTHER CAMPFIRE-BASED MOD will be disabled. Disabling this feature is not recommended.\nIf you are affected by the "brawl bug", try temporarily disabling this feature.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingTutorials	If enabled, Campfire will display certain tutorial messages when it is contextually relevant. If you are already an experienced Campfire player, you can safely disable this feature.\nDefault: On
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingResetTutorials	Reset all contextual tutorials.
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingSelectProfile	Select a Settings Profile where all of your Campfire settings will be saved automatically.\nSettings Profiles are written to a file and persistent across saves, loads, characters, and new games.\nYour last used Settings Profile will be loaded for you when the game starts (if enabled).
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingRenameProfile	Rename the current Settings Profile.
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingEnableSaveLoad	Enable or disable saving your settings to a Settings Profile and loading your current profile when the game starts.\nIf disabled, your settings will no longer be saved or loaded automatically.\nSee "About Settings Profiles" for more information.
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingDefaultProfile	Restore the current profile to default settings.
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingEOCompatibility	Enable or disable an Equipping Overhaul compatibility work-around.\nDefault: Disabled
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingRespec	Select to have all spent skill points refunded.
$CampfireOptionHighlightSettingRestore	Select to restore lost skill point progress.
$CampfireTutorialResetPrompt	Reset all tutorials?
$CampfireTutorialResetDone	Tutorials reset.
$CampfireHelpTroubleshootingSelectProblem	Select Problem:
$CampfireTroubleshooterPrompt	This will run the troubleshooter. You will have to exit the menus in order to complete the troubleshooting procedure. Continue?
$CampfireTroubleshooting0	Select
$CampfireTroubleshooting1	Always says "You are already trying to place something."
$CampfireHelpEnableTutorials	Show Tutorials
$CampfireHelpResetTutorials	Reset Tutorials
$CampfireGuideTopic1Text	To build a campfire, use the Build Campfire ability (by selecting it in the Spell menu and pressing Shout). Campfires can be created from a variety of items, displayed in the crafting menu.\n\nTinder is required to start a campfire. Your choice of tinder determines how long it will take to light your campfire. It is much harder to light a campfire in bad weather, so prepare by carrying some high-quality tinder in case the weather takes a turn for the worse.
$CampfireGuideTopic2Text	Creating or buying supplies can aid you in a wide variety of circumstances. You can create supplies such as tanning racks, torches, basic weapons, and more by using the Survival Skill: Create Item ability.\n\nSome supplies can be purchased at various general goods merchants.
$CampfireGuideTopic3Text	To harvest wood, use Survival Skill: Harvest Wood. If you have a woodcutter's axe or a stone hatchet, you will be able to harvest deadwood.\n\nWithout an axe, you can harvest branches.\n\nEach time you search for resources, an hour will pass.
$CampfireGuideTopic4Text	The amount of additional equipment required to survive in the wilderness can be burdensome. Backpacks can help offset the weight of the additional gear.\n\nBackpacks are created at a tanning rack from a wide variety of pelts. They can be combined with amulets of the Nine Divines to impart certain bonuses and provide additional customization.
$CampfireGuideTopic5Text	Campfire includes a stand-alone skill system to improve your ability to start fires, harvest more resources, improve your Instincts, and more.\n\nTo access the skill system, build a campfire and select Skills. Other Campfire-based mods can add their own skill trees to this menu, like Frostfall and Last Seed.
$CampfireGuideTopic6Text	Instincts allows you to focus on your senses of hearing and smell when outdoors.\n\nWhen Instincts is active, you will see sound emit from creatures (including machines and daedra) up to 100 feet away. You can only "hear" creatures this way when they are moving, talking, or loud (like using a forge). If they are close (at least 50 feet), they can be "heard" even when quiet and still, but the effect is faint.
$CampfireGuideTopic6TextCont	Dead bodies can be "smelled", including the undead. Items in the environment that can be used as tinder for campfires will glow.\n\nThis ability can only be used outdoors, and movement cancels the effect.
$CampfireSaveLoadTopic	Settings Profiles store all of your Campfire configuration settings to a file. Each time you change a setting, that change is automatically saved to your current profile.\n\nWhen you load your game, switch characters, or even start a new game, your last selected profile's settings will automatically be loaded for you. This means less time configuring mods and more time playing the game.
$CampfireSaveLoadTopicCont	You can have more than one profile, and you can name your profiles to make it easier to remember which settings you have stored. There are 10 profile slots available to use. This makes it easy to have saved settings for many different characters and playstyles.\n\nTo turn off this behavior, disable "Automatic Profile Save / Load". Your settings will no longer be saved when changed or loaded on start-up.
$CampfireSaveLoadTopicCont2	Your settings are saved to /skyrim/Data/SKSE/Plugins/CampfireData/. The common.json and profile*.json files contain your profile settings.\n\nIf you use Mod Organizer, your settings will most likely be saved to [Mod Organizer Directory]/overwrite/SKSE/Plugins/CampfireData.
$CampfireEOCompatibilityDetailPrompt	By enabling this option, you allow Campfire to press the Geared Up hotkey for you automatically when sitting or laying down in a tent in order to prevent visual duplication. This is a work-around and is not official support from Campfire or Equipping Overhaul.\n\nThe Geared Up hotkey must be configured in order for this to work!\n\nAre you sure you want to enable this?
$CampfireInstinctsHeaderDetection	Detection
$CampfireInstinctsHeaderEffects	Effects
$CampfireInstinctsSettingFindTinder	Find Tinder Items
$CampfireInstinctsSettingFindFlora	Find Flora
$CampfireInstinctsSettingHearCreatures	Hear Creature Movement
$CampfireInstinctsSettingSmellDead	Smell Dead
$CampfireInstinctsSettingSenseObjective	Sense Path to Next Objective
$CampfireInstinctsSettingVFX	Visual Distortion Effect
$CampfireInstinctsSettingSFX	Sound Effect
$CampfireOptionHighlightFindTinder	If enabled, items that can be used as tinder for campfires will be detected with a yellow glow when using Instincts.\nDefault: Enabled
$CampfireOptionHighlightFindFlora	If enabled, general flora (plants, mushrooms, etc) will be detected with a blue glow when using Instincts. \nDefault: Enabled
$CampfireOptionHighlightHearCreatures	If enabled, creatures that are moving or talking will emit sound waves that can be seen through walls when using Instincts. If close enough, you can detect creatures even when they aren't moving.\nNote: Changes to this setting can take up to 15 seconds to apply!\nDefault: Enabled
$CampfireOptionHighlightSmellDead	If enabled, you will be able to smell dead bodies and the undead when using Instincts.\nNote: Changes to this setting can take up to 15 seconds to apply!\nDefault: Enabled
$CampfireOptionHighlightSenseObjective	If enabled, the path to your next quest objective will be briefly displayed when using Instincts.\nDefault: Disabled
$CampfireOptionHighlightVFX	Toggle the visual distortion effect when starting Instincts on or off.\nDefault: Enabled
$CampfireOptionHighlightSFX	Toggle the sound effect when starting Instincts on or off.\nDefault: Enabled